The Fifth of November is a drama, thriller film
directed by Javier Augusto Nunez.
A psychological thriller following Jane, a survivor of a mass shooting.
As she prepares to celebrate another birthday, the trauma shows itself.
Jane, played by Qurrat Ann Kadwani.
Zachary, played by William H. Bryant Jr..
Owen, played by Shaw Jones.
Alejandra, played by Joanna DeLane.
News Show Host, played by Obaid Kadwani.
Conservative Commentator, played by Meredyth Kenney.
The Fifth of November is a 2018 psychological thriller short film directed by
Javier Augusto Nunez and written by Nunez and Qurrat Ann Kadwani.
The film stars Kadwani, William H.
Bryant Jr., Joanna DeLane and Shaw Jones.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.